<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Soups on Sleek Demo</title>
    <link>https://citations-d-amour.yippee-ki-yay.us/soup/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Soups on Sleek Demo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2020 08:21:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://citations-d-amour.yippee-ki-yay.us/soup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Any-night-of-the-week Sweet stuffed pepper soup</title>
      <link>https://citations-d-amour.yippee-ki-yay.us/soup/963-recipe-of-any-night-of-the-week-sweet-stuffed-pepper-soup/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2020 08:21:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://citations-d-amour.yippee-ki-yay.us/soup/963-recipe-of-any-night-of-the-week-sweet-stuffed-pepper-soup/</guid>
      <description>Sweet stuffed pepper soup
Hello everybody, it is John, welcome to our recipe page. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to make a distinctive dish, sweet stuffed pepper soup. It is one of my favorites. For mine, I am going to make it a bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Stuffed Pepper Soup - all the flavors of a stuffed bell pepper in easy, hearty and comforting soup form!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Super Quick Homemade Meat shells in yogurt soup</title>
      <link>https://citations-d-amour.yippee-ki-yay.us/soup/1447-recipe-of-super-quick-homemade-meat-shells-in-yogurt-soup/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jun 2020 07:10:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://citations-d-amour.yippee-ki-yay.us/soup/1447-recipe-of-super-quick-homemade-meat-shells-in-yogurt-soup/</guid>
      <description>Meat shells in yogurt soup
Hey everyone, hope you&amp;rsquo;re having an incredible day today. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to prepare a special dish, meat shells in yogurt soup. It is one of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I am going to make it a little bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Place yogurt mixture in a large pot. Begin cooking on a low heat. Hamburger Meat and Wild Rice Soup Recipe, Shish barak (meat dumpling in yogurt soup) recipe, Soup with Meat Balls ( Shawrabt el Ima) Recipe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Make Perfect Low Calorie Asian Soup</title>
      <link>https://citations-d-amour.yippee-ki-yay.us/soup/2929-how-to-make-perfect-low-calorie-asian-soup/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 17:18:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://citations-d-amour.yippee-ki-yay.us/soup/2929-how-to-make-perfect-low-calorie-asian-soup/</guid>
      <description>Low Calorie Asian Soup
Hey everyone, hope you are having an amazing day today. Today, I will show you a way to make a special dish, low calorie asian soup. One of my favorites. This time, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna make it a little bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Low Calorie Asian Soup is one of the most favored of current trending foods in the world. It&amp;rsquo;s appreciated by millions daily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easiest Way to Prepare Any-night-of-the-week Lentil &amp; potato pressure cooker vegetable soup</title>
      <link>https://citations-d-amour.yippee-ki-yay.us/soup/494-easiest-way-to-prepare-any-night-of-the-week-lentil-potato-pressure-cooker-vegetable-soup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 03:13:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://citations-d-amour.yippee-ki-yay.us/soup/494-easiest-way-to-prepare-any-night-of-the-week-lentil-potato-pressure-cooker-vegetable-soup/</guid>
      <description>Lentil &amp;amp;amp; potato pressure cooker vegetable soup
Hello everybody, it is John, welcome to my recipe site. Today, I will show you a way to prepare a special dish, lentil &amp;amp; potato pressure cooker vegetable soup. One of my favorites food recipes. This time, I am going to make it a little bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Перевод слова lentil, американское и британское произношение, транскрипция lentil beetle — чечевичная зерновка lentil head — чечевицеобразная головка; линзообразная головка.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Way to Make Any-night-of-the-week Chicken noodle soup</title>
      <link>https://citations-d-amour.yippee-ki-yay.us/soup/3000-simple-way-to-make-any-night-of-the-week-chicken-noodle-soup/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 11:28:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://citations-d-amour.yippee-ki-yay.us/soup/3000-simple-way-to-make-any-night-of-the-week-chicken-noodle-soup/</guid>
      <description>Chicken noodle soup
Hey everyone, it is Brad, welcome to our recipe site. Today, I will show you a way to make a distinctive dish, chicken noodle soup. One of my favorites. For mine, I will make it a little bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Chicken noodle soup is one of the easiest soups to make. The ingredients are simple and inexpensive. My kids love chicken noodle soup, and it&#39;s so easy to pack in a thermos for school lunch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Ultimate Golden Yam with chicken pepper soup</title>
      <link>https://citations-d-amour.yippee-ki-yay.us/soup/640-recipe-of-ultimate-golden-yam-with-chicken-pepper-soup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2020 13:07:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://citations-d-amour.yippee-ki-yay.us/soup/640-recipe-of-ultimate-golden-yam-with-chicken-pepper-soup/</guid>
      <description>Golden Yam with chicken pepper soup
Hello everybody, it is Louise, welcome to our recipe page. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to prepare a special dish, golden yam with chicken pepper soup. It is one of my favorites food recipes. This time, I am going to make it a bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Golden Yam with chicken pepper soup is one of the most well liked of recent trending meals in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easiest Way to Prepare Any-night-of-the-week Chicken Noodle Soup</title>
      <link>https://citations-d-amour.yippee-ki-yay.us/soup/3001-easiest-way-to-prepare-any-night-of-the-week-chicken-noodle-soup/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2020 10:12:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://citations-d-amour.yippee-ki-yay.us/soup/3001-easiest-way-to-prepare-any-night-of-the-week-chicken-noodle-soup/</guid>
      <description>Chicken Noodle Soup
Hello everybody, hope you are having an amazing day today. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to make a special dish, chicken noodle soup. It is one of my favorites food recipes. This time, I will make it a bit tasty. This will be really delicious.
Chicken noodle soup is one of the easiest soups to make. The ingredients are simple and inexpensive. My kids love chicken noodle soup, and it&#39;s so easy to pack in a thermos for school lunch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Step-by-Step Guide to Prepare Perfect Rich potato soup from leftovers</title>
      <link>https://citations-d-amour.yippee-ki-yay.us/soup/1575-step-by-step-guide-to-prepare-perfect-rich-potato-soup-from-leftovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 08:57:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://citations-d-amour.yippee-ki-yay.us/soup/1575-step-by-step-guide-to-prepare-perfect-rich-potato-soup-from-leftovers/</guid>
      <description>Rich potato soup from leftovers
Hello everybody, hope you&amp;rsquo;re having an incredible day today. Today, I will show you a way to prepare a distinctive dish, rich potato soup from leftovers. One of my favorites. This time, I am going to make it a little bit unique. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Rich potato soup from leftovers is one of the most favored of recent trending foods in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Way to Make Speedy Broccoli egg drop soup with prawns</title>
      <link>https://citations-d-amour.yippee-ki-yay.us/soup/357-simple-way-to-make-speedy-broccoli-egg-drop-soup-with-prawns/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 19:33:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://citations-d-amour.yippee-ki-yay.us/soup/357-simple-way-to-make-speedy-broccoli-egg-drop-soup-with-prawns/</guid>
      <description>Broccoli egg drop soup with prawns
Hello everybody, hope you are having an incredible day today. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to make a distinctive dish, broccoli egg drop soup with prawns. It is one of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I am going to make it a little bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Growing up, my family had a tradition of eating lunch at our local little Chinese restaurant every single Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recipe of Homemade Broccoli egg drop soup with prawns</title>
      <link>https://citations-d-amour.yippee-ki-yay.us/soup/4019-recipe-of-homemade-broccoli-egg-drop-soup-with-prawns/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 04:31:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://citations-d-amour.yippee-ki-yay.us/soup/4019-recipe-of-homemade-broccoli-egg-drop-soup-with-prawns/</guid>
      <description>Broccoli egg drop soup with prawns
Hello everybody, it is Brad, welcome to my recipe page. Today, I will show you a way to make a distinctive dish, broccoli egg drop soup with prawns. One of my favorites food recipes. This time, I will make it a bit unique. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
In a large saucepan, combine broth and remaining water. Sup Jagung Telur (Egg Drop Corn Soup).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easiest Way to Prepare Speedy Japanese Red Snapper Soup Noodle</title>
      <link>https://citations-d-amour.yippee-ki-yay.us/soup/1739-easiest-way-to-prepare-speedy-japanese-red-snapper-soup-noodle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 21:34:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://citations-d-amour.yippee-ki-yay.us/soup/1739-easiest-way-to-prepare-speedy-japanese-red-snapper-soup-noodle/</guid>
      <description>Japanese Red Snapper Soup Noodle
Hello everybody, it is Louise, welcome to my recipe site. Today, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna show you how to prepare a special dish, japanese red snapper soup noodle. One of my favorites. This time, I will make it a little bit tasty. This will be really delicious.
Japanese Red Snapper Soup Noodle is one of the most popular of current trending meals in the world. It&amp;rsquo;s enjoyed by millions daily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steps to Make Quick Persian vermicelli soup</title>
      <link>https://citations-d-amour.yippee-ki-yay.us/soup/1553-steps-to-make-quick-persian-vermicelli-soup/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 23:50:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://citations-d-amour.yippee-ki-yay.us/soup/1553-steps-to-make-quick-persian-vermicelli-soup/</guid>
      <description>Persian vermicelli soup
Hello everybody, it&amp;rsquo;s Louise, welcome to our recipe page. Today, I will show you a way to make a special dish, persian vermicelli soup. One of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I am going to make it a little bit tasty. This will be really delicious.
Also Check: Vegetable Soup Recipe Vegan, Healthy &amp;amp; Yum طرز تهیه سوپ سبزیجات خوشمزه Ashpazi ba Sana vermicelli soup Ashpazi ba Sana آشپزی با سنا آشپزی با سنا سوپ ورمیشل.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Way to Make Award-winning Chicken Noodle Soup</title>
      <link>https://citations-d-amour.yippee-ki-yay.us/soup/3320-simple-way-to-make-award-winning-chicken-noodle-soup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 01:46:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://citations-d-amour.yippee-ki-yay.us/soup/3320-simple-way-to-make-award-winning-chicken-noodle-soup/</guid>
      <description>Chicken Noodle Soup
Hey everyone, hope you&amp;rsquo;re having an incredible day today. Today, I will show you a way to prepare a special dish, chicken noodle soup. One of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I will make it a bit tasty. This is gonna smell and look delicious.
Chicken noodle soup is one of the easiest soups to make. The ingredients are simple and inexpensive. My kids love chicken noodle soup, and it&#39;s so easy to pack in a thermos for school lunch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easiest Way to Make Homemade Thick chicken &amp; vegetable soup</title>
      <link>https://citations-d-amour.yippee-ki-yay.us/soup/1134-easiest-way-to-make-homemade-thick-chicken-vegetable-soup/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 20:27:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://citations-d-amour.yippee-ki-yay.us/soup/1134-easiest-way-to-make-homemade-thick-chicken-vegetable-soup/</guid>
      <description>Thick chicken &amp;amp;amp; vegetable soup
Hello everybody, I hope you are having an incredible day today. Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to make a distinctive dish, thick chicken &amp;amp; vegetable soup. It is one of my favorites food recipes. For mine, I will make it a bit unique. This will be really delicious.
Thick chicken &amp;amp; vegetable soup is one of the most favored of recent trending meals on earth. It is easy, it is quick, it tastes yummy.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
